var stages = {
    stage1: {
        data: [
            {
              "question": "Photoelectric effect is associated with?",
              "options": [
                "A: Non-Metals",
                "B: Gases",
                "C: Metals",
                "D: Photosynthesis",
              ],
              "ans": "C"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which of these is not a JavaScript library?",
              "options": [
                "A: jQuery",
                "B: Angular",
                "C: React",
                "D: Immutablejs",
             ],
             "ans": "B"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which is a CSS framework?",
              "options": [
                "A: Popper",
                "B: Modernizr",
                "C: Bootstrap",
                "D: Sass",
              ],
              "ans": "C"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which language is closer to the hardware?",
              "options": [
                "A: Python",
                "B: Hash",
                "C: C++",
                "D: JavaScript",
              ],
              "ans": "C"
            },
            {
              "question": "Who is the creator of Python?",
              "options": [
                "A: Guido van Rossium",
                "B: Brendan Eich",
                "C: Google Inc",
                "D: Dan Abrahmov",
              ],
              "ans": "A"
            },
            {
              "question": "Colourless and odourless is the property of?",
              "options": [
                "A: Calcium",
                "B: Ammonium",
                "C: Chlorine",
                "D: Methane",
              ],
              "ans": "D"
            },
            {
              "question": "Who created the C programming language?",
              "options": [
                "A: Ken Jones",
                "B: Dennis Ritchie",
                "C: Bjarnne Stautroup",
                "D: Tom Smith",
              ],
              "ans": "B"
            }
        ]
    },
    stage2: {
      data: [
          {
            "question": "What is the full meaning of PHP?",
            "options": [
              "A: Hypertext Preprocessor",
              "B: Pre Hypertext Processor",
              "C: Page High Power",
              "D: Power High Page",
            ],
            "ans": "A"
          },
          {
            "question": "In JavaScript which is an abstract data type?",
            "options": [
              "A: Array",
              "B: List",
              "C: Symbol",
              "D: String",
           ],
           "ans": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is a PHP framework?",
            "options": [
              "A: Composer",
              "B: WebGl",
              "C: Mongoose",
              "D: Laravel",
            ],
            "ans": "D"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is the largest country by population?",
            "options": [
              "A: Russia",
              "B: United States of America",
              "C: China",
              "D: Japan",
            ],
            "ans": "C"
          },
          {
            "question": "Flourine element is known as?",
            "options": [
              "A: Halogen",
              "B: Ester",
              "C: Rare gas",
              "D: Ethanol",
            ],
            "ans": "A"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of these is not a framework for building Android application?",
            "options": [
              "A: React Native",
              "B: Ionic",
              "C: Phonegap",
              "D: Kotlin",
            ],
            "ans": "D"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of these is not a metal?",
            "options": [
              "A: Calcium",
              "B: Aluminium",
              "C: Argon",
              "D: Sodium",
            ],
            "ans": "C"
          }
      ]
  },
  stage3: {
    data: [
        {
          "question": "Chai is a tool used for?",
          "options": [
            "A: Testing",
            "B: Module bundling",
            "C: Designing",
            "D: Data Science",
          ],
          "ans": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which is not used for module bundling and task running?",
          "options": [
            "A: Webpack",
            "B: Mocha",
            "C: Gulp",
            "D: Grunt",
         ],
         "ans": "B"
        },
        {
          "question": "Tkinter is a python library used for?",
          "options": [
            "A: Artificial Intelligence",
            "B: Machine Learning",
            "C: Desktop development",
            "D: Mobile development",
          ],
          "ans": "C"
        },
        {
          "question": "Golang was created at?",
          "options": [
            "A: Facebook",
            "B: Zeit",
            "C: Microsoft",
            "D: Google",
          ],
          "ans": "D"
        },
        {
          "question": "Scrapy is a framework used for?",
          "options": [
            "A: Web crawling",
            "B: Game development",
            "C: Network sniffing",
            "D: Web development",
          ],
          "ans": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "Nodejs is usually known for its?",
          "options": [
            "A: Speed",
            "B: Efficiency",
            "C: Simplicity",
            "D: Asyncronousity",
          ],
          "ans": "D"
        },
        {
          "question": "The largest planet is?",
          "options": [
            "A: Saturn",
            "B: Jupiter",
            "C: Earth",
            "D: Uranium",
          ],
          "ans": "B"
        }
    ]
  }
}